How are you?
Where is your wife?
I've got no wife now.
This is why I am asking you because this is the second time now.
If I marry, they run away.
Prophecy Time
That is why I met you and that is the greatest challenge you are facing now.
You have been lonely for some time now.
Almost 20 years.
That is what I am saying.
I am living in England.
I brought two to England; they ran away.
They run away?
The one I married in Nigeria, I brought her there and she ran away.
They run away - almost four now.
You see! So that's why I am just a loner.
But there is a court case.
I want to advise you.
They had dismissed the case in the past.
Yes.
OK. I don't want to say more than that because I don't want anything to distort the case on the ground.
I will see you one on one.
Come here.
Come on.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
There was a test doctor did for you.
Yes.
Is it prostate?
It is prostate.
Prophecy Time
Go and wait for me.
I see this is the third time now.
There was a heat, energy, light they blew into your anus.
Yes.
They said they wanted to...
You have been battling with it for some time now.
Yes, I have been praying over it.
They could have operated on me but I said I did not want the operation.
That is what I am saying.
I said they would have operated you but you said no.
Don't worry.
Go and wait for me.
After receiving the word of prophecy from Prophet T.B. Joshua, Mr. Emmanuel came back to The SCOAN
with his family to be reconciled by the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
As a communicator between the visible and the invisible Prophet T.B. Joshua
exposed the root cause of Mr. Emmanuel's problems through the word of prophecy
given to him by God Almighty.
Let's listen to Mr. Emmanuel as he confirms the prophecy.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
And that is my name too, Emmanuel.
My story is as big as this church.
My name is Emmanuel Nwoye Okpoko.
I live in UK.
I have lived there for 22 years and there is nothing to show for it.
These people are my sons and my grandchildren there.
That woman there is my ex-wife.|
Since 34 years that I separated from this woman, I saw her here in The SCOAN for the first time.
I never knew it could be possible.
Last Sunday, the man of God gave me a prophecy.
He said that I had married and re-married and that I've gotten three wives.
He then asked me where my wife was and I said I didn't have one because really, I have none.
I told him that if I married, they would run away as if I was the ugliest man in the world.
It all started when I wanted to get married.
I was not actually in love with my ex-wife; it was my mother's arrangement.
She said I was going to marry the lady.
I didn't know her but for me to respect my mother's decision, for me to make my mother happy,
I had to marry her.
Actually, when I married her, we were going fine.
Things were going fine until I started making money.
I was into transport business and I started flourishing.
I bought trailers and that was where the trouble started.
I can remember, she used to go to the saloon and I got some experience there.
She would tell me to sign blank cheques for her
so that she could put and figure she liked on my cheques and withdraw money.
I asked her where she got that idea from.
So, trouble started.
"Where did you get that, that I should sign a blank cheque for you to put any figure you like?"
I thought it was a joke.
The hatred increased; there was no month we were in peace.
To cut the story short...
I had two ships at Tin Can Wharf for clearing.
My wharf managers were already there.
I was carrying my briefcase to put inside my car to go to work.
All my sons were young then but they knew what happened.
As I was about to enter the car, she pulled my briefcase and said, "Don't you know that you daughter is sick
and you don’t care, you are going to work?"
I told her that I had introduced a doctor to her, if any of our children were sick
she should take them there for treatment and he would keep my bill for me.
She asked me, "Why?"
From there, trouble started.
And then... she run outside...
She held me and fought me.
She was very big at that time.
I was struggling with her.
Imagine if a woman would have beaten me.
I had to stand on my feet and hit her hard.
She fell down and when she got up, she broke the windscreen of my car
in the front and back and then, ran away.
Obviously, I couldn't control myself so, I took my cutlass.
Yes.
She was lucky that I didn't get her; only God knows what would've happened that day.
After that day, I couldn't take it anymore.
I told my brother to go and get a large vehicle
and pack anything she touched inside it and let her take it home
even though she did not have a dime in my house.
Anything she touched...
Then, I took all of my boys and put them in Santana Private Primary School
where I visited them every two weeks.
I was a single father; I brought up these children single- handedly.
Now, anywhere I go...
I am so emotional.
Anywhere I went, they were pointing that this was the woman destroying my life.
Any business I put together, nothing worked.
The whole thing had affected my children.
My children, these boys that you see, survived by God's mercy.
Nobody is a fraudster or thief; they are just good children.
Imagine a father leaving a country for 22 years and my children were on their own.
Why should I be happy?
I had no wife.
If I married, they ran away and they said it was the same woman who was doing the whole thing - Theresa.
Look at my granddaughter.
I had never seen her.
I only saw her two days ago.
Look at my other granddaughter.
She punished me.
In England, I went everywhere.
There was no witchdoctor I had not gone to.
In short, there was nothing else I could do
until a friend introduced me to The SCOAN.
My son is a very successful businessman but it is always one step forward and three steps back.
When he told me, I said that if I returned to Nigeria, I would butcher this woman.
I would use my cutlass.
If she didn't die through juju (charms), I would use my cutlass to kill her.
My son told me that it was better that I come down.
I told him that I didn't have enough money but he said I should just come.
He said I should go and check how much a ticket cost.
I checked the price and before I knew it, he had paid money into my account.
Without telling anybody, I could not buy anything.
I wondered what I would do to my children and grandchildren.
He told me that shopping was not important at this point.
He had never been to any church.
If I told him about The SCOAN, he would be laughing at me.
He told me that he had heard a lot of things about The SCOAN.
He said that nothing worked and that everyone should defend themselves.
When I came on the 18th, I came to The SCOAN on Sunday.
As I sat down there, I couldn't believe my eyes.
The second person that the man of God touched was me.
He hit the nail on the head and told me all my problems.
I had done so many operations.
I told the doctor concerning my prostate that I would never operate it,
that I had to pray over it because I knew it was dangerous.
He hit the nail on the head and then told me to bring my whole family
because there were more things to be revealed.
I never knew the woman would agree to come to The SCOAN.
I have two daughters in England, both of them are nurses.
The oldest one asked me if it was sure that their mother would come.
I said I didn't know but if she didn't come, I would tell Prophet T.B. Joshua that she is at large
and he would make her to come.
That was what I had in mind.
When I came to Nigeria, I asked my son if he could take me to The SCOAN.
He said he would give me his driver.
He gave me his driver and I came to the church early in the morning.
I told my son what the man of God had said and he said he would follow me.
This is my oldest son.
I told him and he agreed.
My third son is a footballer.
I tried everything for him to come to England but no way.
I spent a lot of money but no way.
He is my third son.
He doesn't talk to me for no reason.
He doesn't even talk to his brothers.
It was from the mum because he was not like this.
This boy saw me after 22 years at The SCOAN and was smiling at me, peacefully.
I carried my grandchildren.
Look at one of them.
I carried the other one in his hand also.
This baby was looking at me, smiling.
She slept in my arms and I wept.
On Thursday we were here.
It is a miracle for me to be able to bring them to The SCOAN today for deliverance.
It is a miracle for me already.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You have listened to that?
That was last Sunday.
When the prophetic service was going on, amidst of the people there, our father was given a message,
exactly as you have heard.
I asked him to wait for me.
I wouldn't like to say much.
I know our father has some impression about our mommy sitting down.
Ogolobo (?)
Everywhere I went, they told me she was a witch.
Pastors and prophets called her names.
You mean that many prophets told you she was a witch?
Yes, but they couldn't do anything.
What is Ogolobo?
Ogolobo means "original witch".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
OK.
How many years ago you saw her last?
34 years.
34 years before you saw her here on Thursday?
34 years before I met her here.
That was after the Sunday service...
Yes, exactly.
... the following Thursday you met her?
Yes, the next Thursday she came.
You know, we are in the presence of God and nothing in hidden.
Our brother, children are standing there and listening.
I want to thank your son, who is not taking sides, he is standing in neutral.
He believes that he is building his own family.
Look at the role our brother plays.
What a role, trying to make sure he is not disconnected from the father or mother.
If not our brother here, we would not be able to sit here and talk
because the whole thing would have gone worse.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If not the role he played, we would not be here today talking about reconciliation, deliverance, prophecy.
He made sure he played the role.
He made sure he invited his father, he even put a money on the account.
He made sure the father comes, and when the father came...
He didn't even say no - he said, "Synagogue, OK - let's go".
He tried to play two roles just like that.
The youth nowadays - we have a lesson to learn.
Because normally we take sides.
Anytime there is trouble between father and mother, instead of you to stand and take a different role...
I mean to stay clear from this matter and do not disconnect from your mother or father.
Our role in the matter of our father and mother actually matters.
If we were able to take a role our brother had taken, the situation would not have come to isolation.
Make sure to see what you can do by keeping praying for them
because they are also your father and your mum.
No matter what happened, no matter the name we call mommy or father - they are the ones giving birth to you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The names prophet and pastor nowadays have become titles.
We shouldn't be carried away by the title or name anybody bears.
A man can be a prophet, pastor or bishop, and yet unbeliever.
So, we still need to ask God.
We shouldn't be carried away, "the prophet or pastor have said that momma is a witch"- no!
We still need to ask God.
In every situation God has something to say.
We need to ask God!
Who is momma by the way?
This is an issue now.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I don’t know where to start but I know I have a lot to say.
My name is Ifeanyi Kenneth Okpoko.
I am the second son of the family.
I happen to be the most doubting of all the Thomases.
In the first place, I rarely go to church.
I have never been a church goer, I don’t even pray.
I just live as every other free man.
I just believe in the laws of nature; you do evil, evil comes to you; you do good, good comes to you.
I have always been a naturalist.
When I met my wife in Kano, she was introduced to me by a family I was supplying goods to.
That was a long time ago, in the year 2000.
One of the things she used to lure me into marrying her, was that she said that she was a Christian.
When talking to her, she would quote the book of James, etc.
Any conversation would end with Christ.
I thought that as I am not a Christian - I was a Christian by birth but not a practising one.
I decided to marry this woman who was very close to God.
It failed because the woman I thought would lead me to God, became something else after I married her.
When we moved to Lagos, she started worshipping in another place.
She went there every Sunday morning.
She would go to church singing praises but come back a wild creature.
She didn’t care about me or the family.
She would not care about my meal.
It continued until I became diabetic in 2005.
I told her about my health status and she didn't care.
She said that I could go and marry someone
who would take care of my diabetes that she didn't bargain for that.
As she got on with her career, it became worse.
She was working with a bank then.
After she started working with UBA.
As her career progressed she became more wild.
If I talked she would shout at me and if I threatened her with separation,
she would say that her job was better without a husband so she was ready to leave.
These things would be happening and each time I spoke with my dad he said that he wanted to come back
and that it appeared as if he and myself shared the same destiny.
I said no, that he just hand to come back; to know what was really going on.
When we were growing up, my dad would be talking about my mum being a witch but
I didn’t want to dwell on that because I didn’t know how to identify a witch.
I tried as much as possible to play my role as a son, both to my mother and father.
If I go to England, my father complains that his work is not good;
he doesn’t know what happens to his money.
Each time I leave him, I give him some money.
When I come back to Nigeria, I call him to see how he is.
If he needs money, from the little I have, I send to him like 2-3000 pounds for his upkeep.
I do the same thing for my mum.
I try to remain very neutral as I know one day God will address the situation.
The first thing I did was to renovate my father's house in the village, which he was building before he left.
Then, I told my dad that I wanted my mum to come back to that house
so that someone would be there to take care of the house.
My dad said he didn't want to see that woman in his territory.
I didn't use force, I just tried to lure him by saying
that we should bring my mum to the house for the sake of keeping it clean.
So, because he listens to me, he agreed to let her come back.
That's how our mum started staying in our house.
Each time we came back, she would come to attend to us.
However, I was a person that didn't believe in miracles.
My dad told me that if he had money, he wanted to return to Nigeria
and the first place he would visit is The SCOAN.
I told him not to believe what he sees on television, that he shouldn't bother.
However, he insisted that when coming to Nigeria, he would go to The SCOAN.
I said, OK and asked whether he wanted money for a flight ticket.
He said that if he had the money, he would enter the next available flight.
I thought he was joking because I had done so many things to bring him back home
but each time I raised the topic, he would tell me one story or the other.
He would make an excuse about kidnapping or poor electricity.
I told him the electricity should not be a barrier as I had a generator in my house.
He asked about transportation, that he needed a car to move around.
I told him not to worry about that as I had cars in my house.
He kept giving one excuse or another.
One thing that made him want to come back was because he wanted to visit The SCOAN.
He said that he was coming back to go to The SCOAN and solve the problem.
I said that as he had said it; the problem is solved.
I didn't have the money he was asking for but I had a friend who normally gave him money in England.
I told him to pay 500 pounds into my dad's account
because my dad said he had found a ticked for about 500 pounds.
I told him that I would reimburse him.
The guy immediately gave him the money and my dad called me that he had received the money.
The next day, he called me and said the 500 pounds ticket would not work,
they said it was 625 pounds but I should not worry as he was going to make up
for the difference; he would get remaining 125 pounds.
I said to myself, "If daddy is talking like this, then there is a miracle on the way".
I thought it was a joke until he called me and said he was in Nigeria.
I didn't believe it.
I called my elder brother to come to my house so that we could drive
straight to the airport because I live very close to the airport.
When my brother came, I told him we were expecting daddy.
He said, "Yes, but until we see him…"
We didn't go to the airport until he was outside at arrivals, calling me on the phone.
We had to rush to go and pick him up.
Behold, it was our dad!
I took him home and told everyone that daddy was around.
The next day he said, "I am going to The SCOAN. Early in the morning, please take me to The SCOAN".
I told him that I didn't like waking up early in the morning, that I was not a church fan
and that any of those prophetic things did not work for me.
My dad said, "You don't want to follow me to The SCOAN and it is very close to your house".
I told him that I didn't want to go, that I would allow my driver to sleep overnight and take him to The SCOAN.
So, I asked my driver to sleep overnight and very early in the morning,
before I had woken up, they had already gone.
When my dad came back about 1:30 am, he said, "Do you know that the man of God spotted me?"
He said that he was the second person spotted be the man of God.
I said, "You? Out of all the congregation and all the people who are coming to The SCOAN,
the man spotted you?"
He said, "Yes".
I told him that I didn't believe him.
He said, "You didn't watch Emmanuel TV?"
I said, "I didn't".
He said, „This man spotted me and the first thing he asked me was, 'Where is your wife?'
So, this man went directly to the problem”.
I said, “What?”
He then said that the man o God said all the family members should come.
I asked him when the next appointment was.
He said that he didn’t know whether it was Thursday or Sunday.
In fact, he was so excited...
I said, “Let it be Thursday”.
I was supposed to travel for a job in the east but said that we should gather the whole family.
He said the first thing he knew was that my mum would not come.
I said, “Well, let us try that”.
I called my mother and told her that there was something going on in T.B. Joshua's church,
very close to where my younger brother lives.
My mum was staying with my younger brother.
The perfect thing about this miracle is that my mum who had always been in the village,
was in Lagos for some months because my younger brother's wife had a baby.
The whole thing was well arranged.
I know how I had been trying to get my mum to come and stay in Lagos but she would not want to stay.
My dad said, “This woman will not come. I bet you she will not come”.
I replied, “Daddy, don’t conclude. Let me invite her”.
I told my mother that her attention was needed in The SCOAN on Thursday.
My mum asked, “How early?”
I told her maybe by 5 am as people were many there.
My mum said, “No problem”.
I called my younger brother who she was staying with.
My younger brother said that he would bring her.
Nobody complained.
Very early, around 5 am, we were here and my mum was there.
Surprisingly, when we went to the canopy, my mum rushed towards my dad for the first time in 34 years
and said, “I want to greet you”.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
Yes, God has spoken.
Who is there to say "no" on "yes"?
[No one.]
OK. The question now is to ask God; whether trillion prophets, or all prophets of the world have spoken...
When God says "yes", no one...
What happened to our mum is a mere affliction.
Everyone also has this affliction.
When I say affliction, it doesn't mean you possess any power, it is rather a fruit of the flesh.
Mommy has that stubborn spirit.
It is not a witch.
This momma is not a witch.
Please baba, it is not a witch.
I want to stand here to say that the steps you have taken so far - no one can blame you for that
because we don't know who is prophet and who is not a prophet.
As a man who runs to ministers of God for a counselling, for a direction -
whatever you hear from them is final.
What you heard did not come from one, two, three... but almost a hundred people saying the same thing.
So, no one can blame you.
My mommy is my mum, she is very stubborn; that's all.
I don't know what to say.
This is the first time in my life that I am believing in a miracle, directly!
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
I used to fall out with my mother.
Each time we would have a quarrel, I would tell her that she was as stubborn as my wife.
I told her that she was very stubborn and that, that was why I married a woman who was like her,
that each time I told her what my wife was doing she would not support me.
She would say, “I don’t want any of my sons to throw away their wives as your father threw me away".
I told her, “Mu daddy threw you away because you are stubborn”.
So, what the man of God said is absolutely true.
I have never said that my mum was a witch.
I always told my father, “Let God be the one to vindicate her”.
Each time my mother is talking...
One thing my mother would say was, “I am not afraid of going anywhere.
If I am a witch, Heaven will see but if I am not a witch, I will live to see the reconciliation of this family".
This is wonderful!
Thank you.
34 years.
Let us blame satan.
Don't blame your husband, your husband also cannot blame you for what happened.
Satan we should blame.
Satan - shame on you.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
I want to host you, people.
I want to join your family.
From now on, I want to join your family, I am a part of the family.
I will leave my 2 bedroom apartment and another 2 bedroom flat for the whole family.
When they leave here, they should set a table and let them meet together.
Baba, I will meet you one on one for counselling - let us talk.
We have to talk.
I want to congratulate you - you have wonderful children.
Even my brother - you say he doesn't greet you.
It is not his fault.
He doesn't know what to do.
He is confused.
He is just confused because the whole thing has affected the children.
The children don't know what to do.
This man is just enjoying the grace of standing, carrying out the little assignment of bringing the family together.
It is not his fault, he doesn't hate you.
You have wonderful children.
I want to thank you very much for your role.
Thank you.
So, momma, you will come back with a testimony.
Please, just sit down.
I am very happy for the whole thing.
I knew before I left England that I would have the last laugh and I am getting it.
Thank you.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I thank God for a day like this.
I thank God for raising a prophet like T.B. Joshua in our time.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
Some of my friends from South Africa, England, call me often to tell me,
“Look, you are living just behind the prophet and people are coming from all over the world to tap from
this anointing and you are so close and you tell me you are a diabetic for eight years”.
I feel pity for myself because if I had known Prophet T.B. Joshua before,
my marriage would not have been a wreck.
But today, I now know and I am standing in this auditorium to tell everybody anywhere in the world,
that whatever I can believe in is very real – any time, any day.
My diabetes has gone!
Anywhere I was going, I would go with drugs, which were always in my pocket.
Even when I was coming to see T.B. Joshua, I needed to eat and take my drugs.
I didn’t believe in anything; I believed in my drugs.
This is gliclazide, this one is galvus (?).
I had been on these drugs for eight years.
I had been languishing…
I don't know, I've been wasting...
Please, I want to see them.
Let the family go and have the time together.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
Earth has no sorrow that Heaven does not feel.
The reconciliation of this family proves that Jesus Christ is concerned about us, wants to be involved
in everything about us, and walk us through whatever live brings.
As Christians, we are commissioned solution providers, and have been given the ministry of reconciliation.
The joy on their faces are evident, as they leave the auditorium
to have their first family meal together in years.
Thank You, Jesus Christ for restoring this broken home.
The Okpoko Family Reconciled
The Okpoko Family Enjoying A Meal Together After Reconciliation
My name is Obiageri Okpoko, the daughter-in-law of Emmanuel Okpoko, which is our daddy.
My mother-in-law is Theresa Okpoko.
I thank T.B. Joshua for this day because it is a great day in this family of Okpoko.
We had been waiting for this day to happen in our lives to see the solution - the end of this problem.
If you had never seen or witnessed such, you would not know that this is a problem.
It is not until it happens to you that you will know that it is a big problem.
I thank Prophet T.B. Joshua for bringing us together.
May the Lord who has put him in this position ensure he is never brought down.
For his generation and all the people who have worked in his ministry,
their story will never remain the same, in the name of Jesus.
In conclusion – Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23).
My name is Ebiseme Okpoko.
I am the wife of the third son.
I would say that I am the happiest person here because I remember when I was getting married to my husband,
my family thought that he never had any family members.
I am so happy because I believe, right now, they will be watching me,
sitting and dining with my husband’s family.
I am very happy.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
It is a wonderful day!
I never believed that in this world, I would be able to toast with my ex-wife.
I never knew it could ever be like this but it has happened!
To be honest, it is a wonderful day for me.
Not only that, I have forgiven her for whatever had happened between us.
My heart is clear.
[Amen!]
Now, she is my wife!
The Okpoko Family Enjoying A Meal Together After Reconciliation
MUST-WATCH Video For EVERY FAMILY!!!
After their glorious reconciliation in Christ Jesus, the Okpoko family spent quality time together
at the faith resort ground of The SCOAN
praying in unity as a family and worshipping God in the beauty of His holiness.
Truly, the Gospel of God's grace changes and challenges everything.
To His power nothing is impossible.
The Okpoko Family Fellowship Together At The Faith Resort Ground
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Okechukwu Francis Okpoko.
I am the eldest son of Mr. Emmanuel Okpoko.
I want to thank God for Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I want to thank God for a day like this.
I never believed in my lifetime that I would be a part of this.
Seeing my mother and father come back together after 34 years, to me, it is more than a miracle.
It is more than a miracle!
My junior brother has said a lot.
I just want to thank God for a day like this.
My name is Ikechukwu Okpoko.
I am the third son.
My brothers have said it all.
I don’t need to say anything much than to say, Emmanuel!
I give Him the glory!
I have seen many prophets but there is no prophet like him.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
Singing In Thanksgiving To God
The Okpoko Family Fellowship Together At The Faith Resort Ground
With the pain of the past gone and forgotten, the family hug themselves and laugh together.
It is hard to imagine that this family had been separated for more than 34 years.
After the word of prophecy from Prophet T.B. Joshua the power of God stepped onto the scene
and broke the spirit of division and unforgivingness, that had held the family in bondage for so many decades.
Following this remarkable reconciliation, the family returned for a joyous testimony the following week.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
Today is a great day for me and I never knew that a day like this would come.
You can see my wife here.
I never realised I could ever be together with her.
I never dreamt that it could be possible.
Her name is Theresa.
My name is Emmanuel Nwoye Okpoko from Anambra State.
Since this problem started, the hatred was so much that I didn't like to see any woman whose name was Theresa.
I didn’t even give them a lift in my car.
If I gave you a lift and your name was Theresa, I would ask you to get out.
You can imagine the weight of the whole thing before I left for England.
One step forward and three steps backward.
I was in England but had nothing to show for it.
Was I the only African man in England?
Anywhere we go they say... you know, sometimes they call names anyway...
I would make money but the money would disappear.
Sometimes...
I would make money, pay it to the bank but when I would go there the next week, the money would be gone.
I never knew that there was a way that things could happen negatively
such that you would be laboring in vain.
For everything, I blamed my wife.
Everything that would happen, I’d blame my wife that she might be the cause.
I was proved wrong last Sunday by the man of God that she was not a witch.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
Most surprisingly, today, when we were on the prayer line
and the wise men were touching us, I was eagerly looking at her.
The first set of wise men came and touched her; nothing happened.
Another set came, touched her but nothing happened.
Up to seven times, she was just calm.
Then I came out of my...
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
I got up from my seat and shook her hands because I was surprised.
Since that Sunday...
Today, I have actually accepted her back.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
For 34 years, we had no contact of any kind.
The hatred had built up.
Today, everything has been cleared.
There is no hatred between us or among our children.
Look at my children and grandchildren.
All of them came out from me and her.
She is the mother of all these children.
I thank God and the man of God for making it real.
I never believed that a day like this would come to pass.
Glory by to God for making it possible for me and my family.
Once again, shall we put our hands together for the Lord Jesus Christ!
Praise the Almighty God!
[Amen.]
My name is Mrs. Theresa Nwamaka Okpoko
This is my second time of entering this church.
I thank Almighty God for T.B. Joshua who vindicated me from the allegations of being a witch,
which had spread to my home-town and among my children.
As God has made it, God knows better than me.
I also thank Almighty God for uniting my with my children and husband.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
My name is Okochukwu Francis Okpoko.
I am the eldest son of Mr. Emmanuel Okpoko.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
I thank God for a day like this and that I am alive to witness this great reunion.
I never believed that I would live to see a day like this.
For 34 years, my parents had been separated and the hatred they had between them was unimaginable.
I think that it is only in The SCOAN that this kind of miracle could happen.
There is no other place in the world...
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
Through the prophecy that the man of God gave him, things started to turn around in our family.
In fact, for the first time ,we prayed and ate together in 34 years.
It is unbelievable!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Kenneth Ifeanyi Okpoko.
I am the second son of the family.
If I was allowed to give testimony continuously,
I would give this testimony for a whole year; every Sunday for one year.
I remain the most amazed of all the members of the family.
Amazed in the sense that I never believed a day like this would come to pass.
When my dad was insisting on coming to Nigeria to The SCOAN, I thought it was one of his false promises
because many times I had tried to bring him home but he had always come up with one excuse or the other.
Surprisingly, this time around, he decided on his own that he was going to come,
that all he wanted me to do was to send the ticket money, if I could afford it.
I said, “Why not?” And I did.
He came into the country on a Thursday.
He started telling me on Saturday evening that I should take him to The SCOAN.
I told him that I didn’t like anything that would disrupt my sleep.
He was talking about waking up at 5am to go to The SCOAN and I have never done that for a very long time.
I could only wake up that early if somebody asked me to collect money for a contract -
that is the truth – not to go to a prophet whom I thought was full of lies and deceit
because that was how I saw prophets all over the country.
I am sorry to say that but that was the reality.
Honestly, it is only in a church like this, as my brother said
because the reunion and prophecy have not only reconciled my family;
it has reconciled my and God because I rarely went to church.
In a nutshell, the disunity had taken a toll on the family.
It disrupted our educational careers because at the time after my mother left the family,
things started working anti-clockwise for my dad.
He tried to marry another wife; the woman came in.
She did her best; she was a wonderful woman as a matter of fact.
She brought us all up the way our dad wanted it but things were not working; they worked anti-clockwise.
My dad had always told us that our mother was a witch
and that she had been against his progress since she left.
When I was growing up, I started playing a very neutral role on the issue,
believing that I did not have any instrument for scanning witches.
I knew that if my dad was correct, one day, God would reveal it to him and
if he was not, one day, God would reveal it to him.
I have always tried to play the role of a son to both parents because that was what mattered.
I had been an unbiased umpire on the matter.
If I saw my dad in England, I tried to make him comfortable as much as I could and
back here in Nigeria, I tried to give my mother all the comfort I could afford,
believing that one day, a day like this would actually come.
I didn’t know it would come so soon.
If I call Prophet T.B. Joshua a prophet, it is an understatement.
I prefer to see him as God incarnate.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
We know you have a lot to say.
But we want it make this point clear that the man of God said, "He is not the Healer, he is not a Deliverer,
he is not a Saviour. He only knows the Saviour, he only knows the Healer, he only know the Deliverer,
who is our Lord and Saviour. He is not Jesus. He is a servant of our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ."
We thank God for using the man of God in this mighty way, to do these mighty things in the lives of the people.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Chinwendu Okpoko.
I happen to be the last child of my mother.
My mother happens to be the second wife of my dad.
Growing up without a dad was really challenging for me.
I remember, way back in primary school if I was asked where my dad was, I really had nothing to say.
It was really challenging for me but I want to bless the name of God for making it possible for me to see
my dad for the first time in my life after how many years.
Could you tell us, how old are you now?
I am 23 years old.
So, for 23 years - you are seeing your father for the first time?
Yes.
Here, at The SCOAN?
Shall we put our hands together for the Lord Jesus Christ!
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ikechukwu Okpoko.
I am the third son.
I thank God for today and I know that whatever God has done is permanent.
Nobody can change it.
I believe one thing about The SCOAN - the prophecies here are very accurate and unmistakable.
I don’t really understand, I am not the man of God but the way he does his things, only God knows.
Everything he says is accurate; and don’t doubt it.
Just don’t doubt it.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
Now, the God has brought unity, peace and comfort into the family.
As Joshua said, him and his family will serve the Lord, we want the whole family to go and serve the Lord
in Spirit and in Truth.
As you do so, the blessings of God will continue to abide in this family, in Jesus' name.
Okpoko Family Reconciliation
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today,
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies from SCOAN
Emmanuel TV; changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.